<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CC Ozkan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CC Ozkan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 16:44:17 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>more thoughts on radio</title>
      <link>/blog/radio-streams-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 16:44:17 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/radio-streams-2/</guid>
      <description>So I wrote about changing my primary listening music source from spotify to online radio streaming before. It is now somewhere around day10-day15 of this experiment, and I&#39;d like to share some more thoughts. In these days, I turned up a station whenever I want to have some rhytmic and melodic sounds in the air. Sometimes I opened spotify or youtube just for listening specific songs. I&#39;ve never to let it play on its own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>beauty of rss</title>
      <link>/blog/beautiful-rss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 12:04:28 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/beautiful-rss/</guid>
      <description>RSS might not be the newest technology in town. But damn it is effecient.
In the age of noice of push notifications, this not disturbing delivery system has became how i consume the internet. From independent blogs (the non-kneelers part of social internet!),to big major publisher sites, podcasts and a lot of other platforms(reddit subreddits, youtube channels, etc) have native rss support. Some additional tools provide rss for non-supporting ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>my rediscovery of radio streams</title>
      <link>/blog/radio-streams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 11:39:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/radio-streams/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, I downloaded all my music and then like everybody else I switched to streaming. Listening tunes from youtube and spotify has its advantages. But I decided to take a step away from it.
There are two reasons behind that escape plan
 listening same stuff over and over again all the &amp;ldquo;explored&amp;rdquo; music is been recommended by the algorithm  Listening music on radio feels way more organic, and has a bit of of surfing taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are the some stuff I&#39;ve made.
  instauto: Bot for scheduling multiple instagram photo posts for multiple accounts. See it here on action!
  rss2insta: Application for automatic posting on an Instagram account from an RSS feed.
  whodis: web app for getting any Instagram user&#39;s profile picture in HD. Check it on here.
  pdfbirlestir.com : web site for merging multiple pdf documents into one file.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>