<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CC Ozkan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on CC Ozkan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 11:39:06 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>my rediscovery of radio streams</title>
      <link>/blog/radio-streams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 11:39:06 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/radio-streams/</guid>
      <description>Years ago, I downloaded all my music and then like everybody else I switched to streaming. Listening tunes from youtube and spotify has its advantages. But I decided to take a step away from it.
There are two reasons behind that escape plan
 listening same stuff over and over again all the &amp;ldquo;explored&amp;rdquo; music is been recommended by the algorithm  Listening music on radio feels way more organic, and has a bit of of surfing taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/blogpodcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogpodcast/</guid>
      <description>About Blog &amp;amp; Podcast So I rarely talk about some stuff on podcast and more rarely try to write on blog, however they are in turkish, so if you speak the language feel free to to look at. Actually you can look at eve if you don&#39;t speek the language too. Why not.
Podcast Yazılar </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo is a static site engine written in Go.
It makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
 Cobra Viper J Walter Weatherman Cast  Learn more and contribute on GitHub.
Setup Some fun facts about Hugo:
 Built in Go Loosely inspired by Jekyll Primarily developed by spf13 on the train while commuting to and from Manhattan. Coded in Vim using spf13-vim  Have questions or suggestions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me, @johndoe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contato</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Me siga em @joaoninguem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are the some stuff I&#39;ve made.
  instauto: Bot for scheduling multiple instagram photo posts for multiple accounts. See it here on action!
  rss2insta: Application for automatic posting on an Instagram account from an RSS feed.
  whodis: web app for getting any Instagram user&#39;s profile picture in HD. Check it on here
  pdfbirlestir.com : web site for merging multiple pdf documents into one file.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projetos</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Em construção&amp;hellip; Aguarde!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sobre Hugo</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Em construção&amp;hellip; Aguarde!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>